import React from 'react'

let halloween = {
    title: "Halloween",
    questions: [
        {   
            question: "This is the day after Halloween",
            answers: ["Allhallowtide", "All Saints Day", "Black X-mass", "All Saints Eve"],
            correct: "All Saints Day"
        },
        {   
            question: "This many pounds of candy corn are made each year",
            answers: ["35 million", "5 million", "15 million", "50 million"],
            correct: "35 million"
        },
        {   
            question: "It's illegal to dress up as a nun for Halloween in this state",
            answers: ["Alabama", "Ohio", "Kentucky", "Utah"],
            correct: "Alabama"
        },
        {   
            question: "This is the most popular US holiday for parties",
            answers: ["4th of July", "Halloween", "Super Bowl", "Thanksgiving"],
            correct: "Super Bowl"
        },
        {   
            question: "According to western thinking, this many witches make up a coven",
            answers: ["7", "4", "9", "13"],
            correct: "13"
        },
        {   
            question: "This candy was originally known as chicken feed",
            answers: ["Tic Tacs", "Skittles", "Candy Buttons", "Candy Corn"],
            correct: "Candy Corn"
        },
        {   
            question: "Halloween is illegal in this country",
            answers: ["Canada", "Germany", "Jordan", "England"],
            correct: "Jordan"
        },
        {   
            question: "This country holds the record for the largest pumpkin ever from 2014",
            answers: ["Canada", "United States", "Russia", "Switzerland"],
            correct: "Switzerland"
        },
        {   
            question: "The phrase Trick-or-Treat was started in this country",
            answers: ["United States", "Canada", "Ireland", "England"],
            correct: "Canada"
        },
        {   
            question: "In California, it is illegal to use this item on Halloween Day",
            answers: ["Firecrackers", "Eggs", "Candles", "Silly String"],
            correct: "Silly String"
        },
        {   
            question: "This is not traditionally used to carve a jack-o-lantern",
            answers: ["Pumpkin", "Potato", "Turnip", "Watermelon"],
            correct: "Watermelon"
        },
        {   
            question: "All of these traits are associated with werewolves except this",
            answers: ["Long middle finger", "Fear of Garlic", "a Unibrow", "Fear of Water"],
            correct: "Fear of Garlic"
        },
        {   
            question: "Halloween's origins date back to this ancient Celtic festival",
            answers: ["Lughnasadh", "Imbolc", "Bealtaine", "Samhain"],
            correct: "Samhain"
        },
        {   
            question: "Guising is a tradition in Ireland and Scotland where people do this",
            answers: ["Pray for Dead", "Bob for Apples", "Fortune Telling", "Trick-or-treat"],
            correct: "Trick-or-treat"
        },
        {   
            question: "A city in this state says there are to be no Halloween celebrations on Sunday",
            answers: ["Montana", "Utah", "Alabama", "Delaware"],
            correct: "Delaware"
        }
    ]
}

export default halloween